<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>
   WIPO Press Releases
  </title>
  <link>
   https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/
  </link>
  <description>
   WIPO Press Releases
  </description>
  <language>
   en
  </language>
  <item>
   <title>
    Investment in Intangible Assets Surges, led by Funding for Software and Databases Amid AI Boom
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0005.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0005.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    Investment in intangible assets such as data, software, brands and other intellectual property-backed assets grew three times faster in 2024 than investment in physical assets such as machinery and buildings, which has languished amid high interest rates and subdued economic recovery, according to new data from the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO) and Italy’s Luiss Business School.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Wed, 09 Jul 2025 08:00:00 +0200
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    WIPO Announces 2025 Global Awards Winners: Recognizing IP-Driven Innovation and Impact
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0007.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0007.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    Ten SMEs and startups are the winners of this year’s WIPO Global Awards, with products including antibody therapeutics, sign-to-speech gloves, next-generation memory chips and sustainable protein fermentation—breakthroughs that reflect the transformative power of intellectual property (IP) in improving lives, advancing technology, and building more sustainable communities.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0200
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Venture Capital Metric Reshapes WIPO's World’s Top 100 Innovation Clusters Rankings
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0008.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0008.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    The addition of venture capital (VC) deal activity as a new metric in this year's WIPO Global Innovation Index (GII) Cluster study has reshaped the ranking with Shenzhen-Hong Kong-Guangzhou overtaking Tokyo-Yokohama to claim the top spot and San Jose-San Francisco moving up three places to third position.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0200
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    WIPO Global Innovation Index 2025: Switzerland, Sweden, US, the Republic of Korea and Singapore Top Ranking; China Enters Top 10; Innovation Investment Growth Slows
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0009.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0009.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    Switzerland, Sweden, the United States of America (US), the Republic of Korea and Singapore top the World Intellectual Property Organization’s Global Innovation Index (GII) 2025 ranking, followed by the United Kingdom, Finland, Netherlands, Denmark and China, which breaks into the top 10 for the first time. Meantime, slowing growth in innovation investments is darkening the innovation forecast, the report found.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Tue, 16 Sep 2025 09:30:00 +0200
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Brazil Makes Contribution to Fund WIPO Projects in Developing Countries
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0010.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0010.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    The Government of Brazil has made a voluntary contribution of BRL1,500,000 (approx.  244,000 Swiss Francs) for WIPO-administered capacity building activities to support the growth of IP use by innovators and creators use across Latin America, the Caribbean and Portuguese-speaking countries in Africa.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:26:00 +0200
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    100 Years of WIPO’s International Design System: Celebrating Iconic Designs for the Ages
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0011.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0011.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    The World Intellectual Property Organization today marked the 100th anniversary of its international design system, celebrating a century of iconic designs that combine utility and beauty.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Thu, 06 Nov 2025 06:54:00 +0100
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    World Intellectual Property Indicators: Global Patent and Design Filings Reach New Records in 2024, Trademarks Flat
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0012.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0012.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    Innovators and designers filed record-setting levels of applications for the intellectual property rights that protect their work in 2024, while demand for the trademarks that promote brands stabilized, according to WIPO’s World Intellectual Property Indicators (WIPI) report.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:30:00 +0100
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    World's Largest IP Survey Reveals Increased Awareness and Trust in IP
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0013.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2025/article_0013.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    Global awareness and trust in intellectual property (IP) systems has reached new heights globally, according to WIPO Pulse 2025, the world's most comprehensive survey of IP perception and awareness.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Thu, 13 Nov 2025 06:43:00 +0100
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    WIPO Coordination Committee Nominates Singapore’s Daren Tang for Second Term as Director General
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2026/article_0001.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2026/article_0001.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    The Coordination Committee of the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO) has nominated Mr. Daren Tang from Singapore for a second six year term to the post of Director General.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0100
   </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    World Intellectual Property Report: Pace of Innovation Diffusion Reaches Historical Heights, But Access, Usage and Capability Gaps Remain
   </title>
   <author>
    WIPO
   </author>
   <link>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2026/article_0002.html
   </link>
   <guid>
    https://www.wipo.int/pressroom/en/articles/2026/article_0002.html
   </guid>
   <description>
    New technologies are spreading across borders at unprecedented pace and gaps are narrowing in how intensively countries are using the innovations, the latest World Intellectual Property Report (WIPR) 2026, Technology on the Move finds.
   </description>
   <pubDate>
    Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:00:00 +0100
   </pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
